Guide to the Sir George Cranfield Berkeley Papers, 1808-1813 MS 011
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series V: Letters from the Admiralty, H. Green, Earl of Mornington, Earl of Mulgrave and others, 1808-1811, 251076
  - Admiralty to G.C.B., 1811 November 12; 251141 (Box 5)
  - Admiralty to G.C.B., 1811 December 7; 251140 (Box 5)
  - Admiralty to G.C.B., 1811 May 22; 251139 (Box 5)
  - Admiralty to G.C.B., 1811 June 4; 251138 (Box 5)
  - M. Greetham to G.C.B., 1811 February 4; 251137 (Box 5)
  - H. Green to G.C.B., 1811 February 14; 251136 (Box 5)
  - H. Green to G.C.B., 1811 February 27; 251135 (Box 5)
  - H. Green to G.C.B., 1811 March 5; 251134 (Box 5)
  - H. Green to G.C.B., 1811 April 27; 251133 (Box 5)
  - H. Green to G.C.B., 1811 June 20; 251132 (Box 5)
  - H. Green to G.C.B., 1811 July 9; 251131 (Box 5)
  - H. Green to George C. Berkeley, 1811 August 2; 251130 (Box 5)
  - H. Green to G.C.B., 1811 October 10; 251129 (Box 5)
  - H. Green to G.C.B., 1811 November 1; 251128 (Box 5)
  - H. Green to G.C.B., 1811 November 19; 251127 (Box 5)
  - H. Green to G.C.B., 1811 November 26; 251126 (Box 5)
  - Hamilton Hamilton to G.C.B., [n.d. ca. 1811]; 251125 (Box 5)
  - Hamilton to G.C.B., 1811 March 13; 251124; Copy (Box 5)
  - Hamilton to G.C.B., 1811 March 19; 251123 (Box 5)
  - Charles MacDonald to G.C.B., 1811 March 4; 251122 (Box 5)
  - William Wellesley-Pole, 3rd earl of Mornington to G.C.B., 1808 December 22; 251121 (Box 5)
  - Mornington to G.C.B., 1809 January 17; 251120 (Box 5)
  - Mornington to G.C.B., 1809 February 1; 251119; Copy (Box 5)
  - Mornington to G.C.B., 1809 February 3; 251118 (Box 5)
  - Mornington to G.C.B., 1809 February 13; 251117 (Box 5)
  - Mornington to G.C.B., 1809 February 14; 251116 (Box 5)
  - Mornington to G.C.B., 1809 February 15; 251115 (Box 5)
  - Mornington to G.C.B., 1809 February 16; 251114 (Box 5)
  - Mornington to G.C.B., 1809 February 23; 251113 (Box 5)
  - Mornington to G.C.B., 1809 February 23; 251112 (Box 5)
  - Mornington to G.C.B., 1809 February 23; 251111 (Box 5)
  - Mornington to G.C.B., 1809 February 23; 251110 (Box 5)
  - Mornington to G.C.B., 1809 February 24; 251109 (Box 5)
  - Mornington to G.C.B., 1809 February 25; 251108 (Box 5)
  - Mornington to G.C.B., 1809 March 13; 251107 (Box 5)
  - Mornington to George C. Berkeley, 1809 March 23; 251106 (Box 5)
  - Mornington to G.C.B., 1809 March 27; 251105 (Box 5)
  - Mornington to G.C.B., 1809 March 27; 251104 (Box 5)
  - Mornington to G.C.B., 1809 April 4; 251103 (Box 5)
  - Mornington to G.C.B., 1809 April 10; 251102 (Box 5)
  - Mornington to G.C.B., 1809 April 19; 251101 (Box 5)
  - Mornington to G.C.B., 1809 May 11; 251100 (Box 5)
  - Mornington to G.C.B., 1809 May 22; 251099 (Box 5)
  - Mornington to G.C.B., 1809 May 24; 251098 (Box 5)
  - Mornington to G.C.B., 1809 May 25; 251097 (Box 5)
  - Mornington to G.C.B., 1809 July 7; 251096 (Box 5)
  - Mornington to G.C.B., 1809 July 7; 251095 (Box 5)
  - Mornington to G.C.B., 1809 July 7; 251094 (Box 5)
  - Mornington to G.C.B., 1809 July 18; 251093 (Box 5)
  - Mornington to G.C.B., 1809 July 29; 251092 (Box 5)
  - Mornington to G.C.B., 1809 August 2; 251091 (Box 5)
  - Mornington to G.C.B., 1809 August 2; 251090 (Box 5)
  - Mornington to G.C.B., 1809 August 4; 251089 (Box 5)
  - Mornington to G.C.B., 1809 August 11; 251088 (Box 5)
  - Mornington to G.C.B., 1809 August 15; 251087 (Box 5)
  - Mornington to G.C.B., 1809 September 13; 251086 (Box 5)
  - Henry Phipps, 1st earl of Mulgrave to G.C.B., 1808 December 12; 251085 (Box 5)
  - Mulgrave to G.C.B., 1808 December 21; 251084 (Box 5)
  - Mulgrave to G.C.B., 1809 February 12; 251083 (Box 5)
  - Mulgrave to G.C.B., 1809 May 13; 251082 (Box 5)
  - Mulgrave to George C. Berkeley, 1809 July 10; 251081 (Box 5)
  - Mulgrave to G.C.B., 1809 December 1; 251080 (Box 5)
  - Mulgrave to G.C.B., 1809 December 7; 251079 (Box 5)
  - Mulgrave to G.C.B., 1810 March 3; 251078 (Box 5)
  - Mulgrave to G.C.B., 1810 April 17; 251077 (Box 5)
- Series VI: Letters From Baron Stuart de Rothesey and others, 1811, 250959
  - Hamilton Rea to G.C.B., 1811 February 11; 251075 (Box 6)
  - Sir Charles Stuart, Baron Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 n.d.; 251074 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 n.d.; 251073 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 January 3; 251072 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 January 3; 251071 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 January 8; 251070 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 January 12; 251069 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 January 20; 251068 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 January 25; 251067 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 January 25; 251066 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 January 25; 251065 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 January 25; 251064 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 January 26; 251063 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 January 26; 251062 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 January 30; 251061 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 January 31; 251060 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 February 2; 251059 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 February 4; 251058 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to George C. Berkeley, 1811 February 5; 251057 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 February 9; 251056 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 February 19; 251055 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 February 19; 251054 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 February 20; 251053 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 February 21; 251052 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 February 22; 251051 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 February 22; 251050 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 February 25; 251049 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 February 25; 251048 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 February 26; 251047 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 February 27; 251046 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 February 27; 251045 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 March 1; 251044 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 March 6; 251043 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 March 7; 251042 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 March 8; 251041 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 March 11; 251040 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 March 14; 251039 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 March 15; 251038 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 March 15; 251037 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 March 15; 251036 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 March 15; 251035 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 March 15; 251034 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 March 15; 251033 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to George C. Berkeley, 1811 March 16; 251032 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 March 16; 251031 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 March 17; 251030 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 March 18; 251029 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 March 18; 251028 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 March 19; 251027 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 March 19; 251026 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 March 19; 251025 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 March 22; 251024 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 March 27; 251023 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 April 3; 251022 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 April 4; 251021 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 April 5; 251020 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 April 5; 251019 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 April 5; 251018 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 April 7; 251017 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 April 16; 251016 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 April 19; 251015 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 April 24; 251014 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 April 24; 251013 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 April 24; 251012 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 April 24; 251011 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 April 24; 251010 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 April 24; 251009 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 April 25; 251008 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to George C. Berkeley, 1811 April 26; 251007 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 April 30; 251006 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 May 2; 251005 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 May 3; 251004 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 May 5; 251003 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 May 5; 251002 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 May 6; 251001 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 May 19; 251000 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 May 25; 250999 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 May 26; 250998 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 May 26; 250997 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 May 29; 250996 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 June 7; 250995 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 August 2; 250994 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 August 2; 250993 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 August 3; 250992 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 September 11; 250991 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 September 17; 250990 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 September 25; 250989 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 October 4; 250988 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 October 10; 250987 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 October 10; 250986 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 October 12; 250985 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 October 17; 250984 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 October 25; 250983 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to George C. Berkeley, 1811 October 27; 250982 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 November 2; 250981 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 November 3; 250980 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 November 4; 250979 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 November 4; 250978 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 November 6; 250977 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 November 6; 250976 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 November 12; 250975 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 November 13; 250974 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 November 25; 250973 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 December 2; 250972 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 December 9; 250971 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 December 12; 250970 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 December 16; 250969 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 December 16; 250968 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 December 17; 250967 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 December 18; 250966 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 December 19; 250965 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 December 23; 250964 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 December 23; 250963 (Box 6)
  - Stuart de Rothesay to G.C.B., 1811 December 26; 250962 (Box 6)
  - William Waldron to G.C.B., 1811 November 21; 250961 (Box 6)
  - Sir John Ferdinand von Zetten to G.C.B., 1811 March 12; 250960 (Box 6)
- Series VII: Transport tonnage stmt. and letter from Lord Castlereagh, 1809 (2 items), 250956
  - Statement of transport tonnage from the Transport Office to G.C.B., 1809 May 7; 250958 (Box 6)
  - Letter from Lord Castlereagh to the Lords Commissioners of the Admiralty, 1809 May 22; 250957; Copy (Box 6)
- Series VIII: Letters from Wellington, 1809-1811, 250823
  - Arthur Wellesley, 1st duke of Wellington to G.C.B., 1809 April 25; 250955 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1809 May 2; 250954 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1809 May 7; 250953 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1809 May 8; 250952 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1809 May 17; 250951 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1809 May 27; 250950 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1809 May 29; 250949 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1809 May 31; 250948 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1809 May 31; 250947 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1809 June 1; 250946 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1809 June 7; 250945 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1809 June 10; 250944 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1809 June 12; 250943 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1809 June 21; 250942 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1809 June 21; 250941 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1809 June 23; 250940 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1809 June 30; 250939 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1809 July 6; 250938 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1809 July 14; 250937 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to George C. Berkeley, 1809 August 27; 250936 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1809 September 12; 250935 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1809 September 16; 250934 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1809 September 21; 250933 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1809 September 23; 250932 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1809 September 26; 250931 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1809 September 28; 250930 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1809 October 11; 250929 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1809 October 28; 250928 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1809 November 20; 250927 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1809 November 20; 250926 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1809 November 28; 250925 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1809 November 30; 250924 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1809 December 7; 250923 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1809 December 7; 250922 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1809 December 19; 250921 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1810 May 1; 250920 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1810 May 2; 250919 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1810 May 3; 250918 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1810 May 8; 250917 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1810 May 12; 250916 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1810 May 23; 250915 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1810 May 29; 250914 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1810 June 1; 250913 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1810 June 22; 250912 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to George C. Berkeley, 1810 June 24; 250911 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1810 June 27; 250910 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1810 July 13; 250909 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1810 July 18; 250908 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1810 July 29; 250907 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1810 August 8; 250906 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1810 August 18; 250905 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1810 August 19; 250904 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1810 September 2; 250903 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1810 September 7; 250902 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1810 September 9; 250901 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1810 September 14; 250900 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1810 December 31; 250899 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1811 January 6; 250898 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1811 January 11; 250897 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1811 January 11; 250896 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1811 January 11; 250895 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1811 January 18; 250894 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1811 January 22; 250893 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1811 January 28; 250892 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1811 January 29; 250891 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1811 January 30; 250890 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1811 February 3; 250889 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1811 February 4; 250888 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1811 February 6; 250887 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to George C. Berkeley, 1811 February 9; 250886 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1811 February 10; 250885 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1811 February 16; 250884 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1811 February 18; 250883 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1811 February 21; 250882 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1811 February 23; 250881 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1811 February 27; 250880 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1811 February 28; 250879 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1811 March 5; 250878 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1811 March 8; 250877 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1811 March 15; 250876 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1811 March 20; 250875 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1811 March 20; 250874 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1811 March 20; 250873 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1811 March 25; 250872 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1811 March 30; 250871 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1811 March 30; 250870 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1811 March 31; 250869 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1811 April 8; 250868 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1811 April 14; 250867 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1811 April 25; 250866 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1811 May 14; 250865 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1811 May 25; 250864 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1811 May 28; 250863 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1811 May 29; 250862 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to George C. Berkeley, 1811 May 31; 250861 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1811 June 5; 250860 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1811 June 20; 250859 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1811 June 23; 250858 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1811 June 25; 250857 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1811 June 26; 250856 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1811 June 30; 250855 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1811 June 30; 250854 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1811 July 2; 250853 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1811 July 3; 250852 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1811 July 4; 250851 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1811 July 5; 250850 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1811 July 6; 250849 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1811 July 7; 250848 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1811 July 8; 250847 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1811 July 17; 250846 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1811 July 22; 250845 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1811 July 25; 250844 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1811 July 25; 250843 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1811 July 25; 250842 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1811 July 27; 250841 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1811 July 29; 250840 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1811 September 2; 250839 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1811 September 7; 250838 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1811 October 4; 250837 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to George C. Berkeley, 1811 October 4; 250836 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1811 October 6; 250835 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1811 October 13; 250834 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1811 October 16; 250833 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1811 October 23; 250832 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1811 October 23; 250831 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1811 November 22; 250830 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1811 November 26; 250829 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1811 December 2; 250828 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1811 December 17; 250827 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1811 December 29; 250826 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1811 December 29; 250825 (Box 7)
  - Wellington to G.C.B., 1811 December 29; 250824 (Box 7)
- Series IX: Letters to Wellington, 1809-1811, 250810
  - George C. Berkeley to [Arthur Wellesley, 1st duke of Wellington], n.d.; 250822 (Box 7)
  - G.C.B. to Wellington, --- July 10; 250821 (Box 7)
  - G.C.B. to Wellington, 1809 May 29; 250820 (Box 7)
  - G.C.B. to Wellington, 1810 September 15; 250819; Copy (Box 7)
  - Lord Castlereagh to Wellington, 1809 May 22; 250818 (Box 7)
  - Lord Castlereagh to Wellington, 1809 September 14; 250817; Copy (Box 7)
  - George W. Hinley to [Wellington], 1809 May 25; 250816 (Box 7)
  - Extract of a letter from Earl of Liverpool to Wellington [Wellington's hand?], 250815 (Box 7)
  - Extract of a letter from Earl of Liverpool to Wellington, 1810 July 25; 250814 (Box 7)
  - [Rudcliffe] to Wellington, 1809 July 6; 250813 (Box 7)
  - W.H. Wellesley to Wellington, 1811 October 14; 250812 (Box 7)
  - [?] to Wellington, --- May 26; 250811 (Box 7)
- Series X: Troop lists and report, 1809-1811 (4 items), 250805
  - Report to Wellington [from Berkeley?], n.d.; 250809; Copy (Box 7)
  - Return of troops lists, 1809 February 9; 250808 (Box 7)
  - Return of troops lists, 1809 February 10; 250807 (Box 7)
  - Transports to proceed to England, 1811 March 28; 250806 (Box 7)